Autosol has come with 2 new ones and I have only tested one so far.
There is one that is only for aluminum and should test it with.
There are other means that you use that act as a wax.
There are 2-3 different brands on the market but I have not been able to try anything yet.
-There's happened to some time since last time.
Yes rims and tires are in place and so did the whole car.
The tires I have offended myself down here.
I bought iron so I could squeeze them.
Both front and rear tires have inner hose and I get punctured along the road ...
... then spare wheels are not enough, but you have to change the inner hose.
And then I have to know if it is possible to push the tire or not and I have practiced all 4 tires.
-And now the grill is ready.
Yes, I have roughly polished to see all the bumps.
If you feel like this, it feels uneven.
I will smooth more but now I know what is visible and not visible.
I have made some covers to sit on the inside of the frame.
These are these.
-And you have pressed this?
Yes and it should sit 2 screwed here.
It is to cover the ugly.
The plastic foil goes around the edge here.
Because I will foil the frame ...
... it is difficult to foil the inside and get it neat.
Even when setting the ignition on the engines.
Distributers are behind here.
-How often will you use this?
I drive as much as the other cars, it is 600 miles a year
-Oops.
If it doesn't work, I put it in a barn where no one can see it.
It should work otherwise it is not fun.
It is pointless to have a car standing.
I want to be able to drive to Stockholm, Norrtälje on a meeting and home.
-What are you putting on now?
These are the oil filling pipes.
It's a bit tight.
It will be the first and second engine and here you fill the oil.
The screws are also new in stainless steel.
I have rationalized away the choke.
This is never used in Sweden in the summer.
I never drive in the winter with this car.
-How should you be able to get carburetors to be sync?
They do not have to be synced because the carburetor in the middle feeds both engines.
Both engines have the same structure and the same compression and camshafts.
That carburetor controls both engines.
During normal driving, only the carburetor in the middle is connected.
When you gas on when overtaking, the other carburetors open.
There will be an exchange here.
It is also own manufacturing.
The most important thing is that when driving at 100-110km/h that the carburetor is set correctly.
It is own implementation here.
It is a piece of leather that I have shrunk.
I got the funnel -shaped and squeezed it between two trays.
And made this brass ring so it gets air tight.
It is the details that do it.
-It really is.
If you want to be won I have made a gap here.
There should be a cable in this hole that is controlled with a lever from the inside.
And it opens that way.
-Of course!
We'll see if it works because it can leak a little.
There will be stainless steel feathers.
These are just ordinary Biltema feathers.
-In terms of body it is clear.
Yes doors and seats are cut.
I have done grid templates and most of the fitting is done.
-What is it for boxes?
-It's not going to be glass?
Well there will be slats.
That I will cut myself.
It doesn't get that far on the pedal.
There is no oil in but this one is connected.
And here is full gas.
-When will it get there?
I'll just buy a regular tachometer that I attach to the back.
And a pointer from a mora clock ...
... a little bigger as an arrow and old numbers as it was on watches before scaled up to 6.
And some lamps at the bottom for charging temp etc.
Should you have any speedometer?
No, there will be GPS instead.
I don't need any speedometer in this car.
And GPS you have with you so I can drive after it.
-I haven't seen any name on it.
It's going on and should ... would cast first ...
... and put on the back but I have regretted it.
It will be in the valve cover instead.
It will be written here.
So you only use plain salt water.
Mask and switch on a car battery.
Plus here and minus you dip in the water.
Here it has become a good edge.
It's only 20 minutes.
It is a very significant edge.
The text should be polished but the frame around.
-What should it be hot?
Uh, Decimo Segundo.
It was sick near the wheel.
Yes it should be corrected.
I have to put a spacer in between so I get the wheel 1.5 cm.
It does not get that hot as it is silencer insulation.
So it insulates the heat with.
What is left to construct is a handbrake.
I have not decided yet and I will have a foot brake or a long lever.
It's good to have an emergency brake.
-Now I'll wage further we'll be visible again soon.
We'll do that.
Bye!
Hello!